-Here you go.
-Thank you.
"Say, Rachel...
...I was wondering if you'd
go to a movie with me sometime...
...as my lover."
Too out there.
"Maybe you'd like to have
dinner with me sometime...
...as my lover."
All right, let's go shopping.
Before we go, there's something
I need to say.
I've kind of had this crush on you.
Since you were with Ross,
I didn't do anything about it.
Now that you're not, I'd really
like to ask you out sometime.
So that's what I'm doing...
... now.
I dropped a cup.
The One With the Tiny T-Shirt
So within a few years,
voice recognition...
...will be standard
on any computer.
You know, so you could be, like,
"Wash my car." "Clean my room."
It won't be able to do any of those
things, but it'll understand.
Oh, this was so great.
Yeah, it was.
All right, then.
Bye.
Hello, people who do not live here.
I gave you a key for emergencies.
We were out of Doritos.
Hey, how'd the date go
with Mr. Millionaire?
"Mr. Millionaire.
New, from Snooty Playthings.
Third wife sold separately."
He's great. We have such
a good time together.
He's so funny and so sweet.
And I'm not attracted to him at all!
Still?
It's driving me crazy. In every
other way, he's the perfect guy.
He has everything.
Plus, he actually has everything.
Life-sized lmperial Storm Troopers
from Sharper lmage?
Two.
Can Joey and I put them on and fight?
Oh, Mommy! Oh, Daddy!
I am a big old baddy
I guess he must've gotten the part
in that play.
Either that, or Gloria Estefan
was right.
Eventually, the rhythm
is going to get you.
-Joe, how's it going?
-Good.
So you're playing Adrianne?
Yes. Are you one of the
retarded cousins?
No. I'm playing your husband, Victor.
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Kate Miller.
So the play's pretty great, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I love Jennifer Banberry's work.
She's so incisive when it comes
to deconstructing the middle class.
Oh, forget about it. She rocks!
Where do I know you from?
Dr. Drake Ramoray?
Days of our Lives?
Voted most datable neurosurgeon
by Teen Beat?.
No, that's not it.
So you're a soap actor.
This must be exciting for you,
being in a real play.
Hey, I've done plays before.
I'm a serious actor.
That infomercial!
For the milk-carton-spout thing!
You're the guy who doesn't
know how to pour milk!
I actually can pour milk. But I got
you believing that I couldn't.
Now, see, that's acting.
Right. At the end, you choked
on a cookie.
That was real.
-I cannot believe Mark asked you out.
-I know.
What are you gonna tell him?
I told him I would think about it,
but I'm gonna tell him no.
I think I'd say no
to anybody right now.
But it was so strange.
I mean, I'm standing there...
...with this charming, cute guy
who's asking me to go out with him...
...which I'm allowed to do...
...and I felt guilty, like I'd be
cheating on Ross or something.
Wow. So, okay, maybe that means...
...you're not over Ross yet
and you have issues with your father.
-I don't have issues with my father.
-So it's just the Ross thing.
I hate this woman! I hate her!
She told everyone
about that infomercial...
...and now they all keep asking me
to open their drinks!
And whenever I can't do it,
they're all, like, laughing at me!
So Rachel called.
Wants to see me.
Going over in a minute.
-What do you think she wants?
-Maybe the crazy fog has lifted...
...and she realizes that life
without me...
...sucks.
It's possible. You are very lovable.
I'd miss you if I broke up with you.
Just trying to be supportive.
Be supportive like a guy.
If I broke up with you, I'd miss you.
You wanted to see me?
Here's a box of your stuff.
It's just hats and a shirt and CD's.
Just stuff that you've left here.
What are you doing? Are you trying
to hurt me or something?
It just seems that, you know,
it's time we move on.
I mean, don't you think?
-Yes, I do.
-Good.
I really do.
This was a gift.
You got that for free
from the museum gift shop.
It's still a gift.
I got it from the "gift" shop.
Okay! All right! Give me the mug!
I'll keep the mug!
Don't do me any favors.
In fact...
...where's the rest of my stuff?
Like my....
This book is mine!
And that T-shirt you sleep in?
I'd like that back too. Yes, I do.
You know how much I love that T-shirt.
You never even wear that T-shirt.
I'm just trying to help you "move on."
Oh, you are a petty man.
You are a petty, petty...
-Petty...
-... petty, petty...
-...small....
You are so just doing this
out of spite.
I'm gonna wear this all the time!
I love this shirt!
You haven't worn it since you were 15!
It doesn't even fit you anymore!
If you don't mind, I'm gonna
take the rest of my stuff...
...and "relax"...
...in my favorite shirt.
You have a pleasant evening.
So you're, like, a zillionaire.
And you're our age.
You're our age.
You know what?
You should buy a state...
...and then just name it
after yourself.
Like, "Pete Dakota"?
Or "Mississi-Pete."
I got it: "Pete Chicago."
That's not a state, Joe.
Oh, and "Mississi-Pete" is?
I gotta go.
I'll see you guys later.
You're our age.
So are we on for tomorrow?
Absolutely.
Now, get out of here, you!
Okay, I'm running out of places
I can touch him.
Is something wrong with me?
Why am I only attracted to guys
with no future?
Either they're too old,
or they're too young.
And there's Pete,
who's crazy about me...
...and he's absolutely perfect,
and there's zip going on!
Does it sound like
something's wrong with me?
Yeah, kind of.
Happy? Is that what I'm
supposed to be, Vic?
Happy?
Why don't you tell me what
you're supposed to be?
Because I sure as hell can't
figure it out!
I talk to you, and nothing!
You look at me, and it's nothing!
Nothing.
Tasty.
I'm really starting to feel like
you guys have a history. It's nice.
I have a question about this scene.
I don't understand why Adrianne's
attracted to Victor.
Peel the onion.
First of all, he's good-looking.
My character needs a bit more
of a reason than that.
Hey, how about this one?
It says so in the script!
I don't know why my character
likes you either.
I mean, it says in the script
that you're a bitch.
-lt doesn't say that in the script.
-lt does in mine.
I can blow-dry it, gel it.
It doesn't matter.
I still wind up with this little...
...cowlick-y thing on the middle part
of my head. It's so annoying.
-Does it bug you?
-You bug me.
Is there any chance
you didn't see that?
Ross, you gotta stop, okay?
You can't stare through
the peephole for three hours.
You're gonna get peep-eye.
I knew it. I knew it.
I always knew she liked him.
She'd say no, but here we are. We just
broke up, first thing she does!
You didn't "just break up."
It's been, like, three weeks!
You slept with somebody three hours
after you thought you broke up.
I mean, bullets have left guns slower.
Here they come! Here they
If she kisses him good night,
I'll kill myself.
I can't watch.
Come on.
Date over! Date over!
Here we go. She's going in.
She's going in.
Wait! He's going in!
He's going in!
The door's closed! I can't see
anything with the door closed!
And the inventor of the door
rests happily in his grave.
I have to do something.
I have to stop it!
-Stop what?
-I don't know.
But I have a feeling
my being there will do it.
I'll go over and I will
borrow something!
Juice! I need juice!
You can't!
-They must be stopped!
-I am your friend...
...and I won't let you do this!
You are surprisingly strong!
-I need juice! People need juice!
-Look, man....
-People need juice!
-Listen to me!
She's moving on. If it's not
this guy, it's gonna be somebody else.
And unless you're thinking about
subletting my peephole...
...you'll have to get used to the fact
that it's over!
Okay, man? It's over.
It's just I miss her so much.
I know.
Why do your coffee mugs have numbers?
Oh, that's so Monica can keep track.
So if one of them's missing,
she can be like, "Where's number 27?"
You know what?
No, and I don't think
I'm gonna want to.
-I can't do this.
-That's what I didn't want to know.
Oh, I'm just doing this
for the wrong reasons, you know?
I'm doing it to get back at Ross.
I'm sorry. It's not very fair to you.
Fair, shmair. You know?
You wanna get back at Ross,
I am here for you.
Really.
I say we get back at him right here
on this couch. Right here!
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry about this.
That's okay.
You sure?
I can just go home and get back
at him by myself.
and should become the penicillin
of the 2 1st century.
And so today, this hospital
is about to take major steps...
...toward leading that revolution.
Can I ask you something?
Where are we?
Well, with all these doctors
and nurses...
... I'm gonna say, "Midget Rodeo."
Just tell me the truth.
You know, I don't think
I told you this...
... but I just recently got out
of a serious relationship.
Oh, right.
Wasn't that a year ago?
So I did tell you.
That's not really the thing.
I'm just in a place in my life
where I need to focus on me.
-Do you know what I mean?
-Oh, I know.
-I so want to be attracted to you.
-But you're not. Okay. Good.
I'm sorry.
You know what? Don't be.
Don't be, because it's not so bad.
It's not?
Yeah. I know I'm no Jon Bon Jovi.
Or someone you find attractive.
I just think, you know...
...that you might end up
feeling differently.
I don't want this
to come out wrong...
...but you're awfully confident for a
guy I said I wasn't attracted to.
Stupidly charming, isn't it?
You wanna get something to eat?
This place is kind of depressing.
Now the man who made all of this
possible, Mr. Peter Becker.
One second.
I don't think this town is big enough
for the both of us to relax in.
Draw!
I wasn't doing anything.
What did she do now?
Just because she went to Yale, she
thinks she's the greatest actress...
...since sliced bread.
Ah, Sliced Bread.
A wonderful Lady Macbeth.
I hate her. I hate her
with her "Oh, I'm so talented"...
...and "Oh, I'm so pretty,"
and "Oh, I smell so good."
I think somebody has a crush
on somebody.
Can we please try and stay focused
on my problem here?
I'm talking about you,
you big, big freak.
You're out of your mind!
You've done nothing but talk
about her for 48 hours.
If you were in school, you'd be pulling
her pigtails and pushing her down now.
Then how come I keep thinking
about her...
...in all these sexual scenarios
and stuff?
Happy? Is that what I'm
supposed to be, Vic? Happy?
Why don't you tell me what
you're supposed to be, huh?
Because I sure as hell can't
figure it out.
I talk to you, and it's nothing.
You look at me, and nothing.
Nothing.
You guys make me fly!
High!
Okay, we're gonna pick it up
here, tomorrow.
-Well, that was....
-Better?
Yeah, it was definitely...
...an improvement.
-Good night.
-Kate.
You forgot your shoes.
I'm probably gonna need those, huh?
Hey, listen...
...you feel like getting
a cup of coffee?
Kate...
...you ready to go?
Very nice. Very nice.
-See you tomorrow?
-Yeah. Sure.
-Right.
-Good night.
Why isn't it "Spiderman"?
Like Goldman, Silverman?
Because it's not his last name.
It isn't?
It's not, like...
... Phil Spiderman.
He's a Spider-...
... man.
You know, like, Goldman
is a last name.
But there's no Gold Man.
There should be a Gold Man!
-How was work?
-Oh, great.
Although I did sit down
where there wasn't a chair.
By the way, Ross dropped by
a box of your stuff.
Oh. Well, I guess I had
that one coming.
I'm just gonna throw it out.
It's probably just shampoo and
Something wrong?
No. Nothing.
So what kind of powers
would "Gold Man" have?
Okay. Well, he would turn things
to gold.
-And things that are already gold?
-His work is done.
Let's play my game.
All right, you yellow-bellied,
lily-livered
Draw!
Yeah, it's fun.